2627 W. Baseline Road #125 Tempe, AZ 85283

# Brandon L. Olson

www.linkedin.com/in/brandonleeolson

C: 1-(907)-414-4455 Olson.L.Brandon@gmail.com

**Executive Summary** 

Works effectively with a variety of different languages, platforms, environments, paradigms, and workflows. Works well individually or in groups, both in leadership and subordinate roles. Passionate about pushing the boundaries of the understanding of computer science and gaining industry experience.

# **Languages and Technologies**

• Java

• C#

• C/C++

Python

• SQL

• HTML

PHP

• x86 Assembly

• Visual Studio

JetBrains

• Scene Builder 2.0

Git

Maven

• Gradle

• Microsoft Office

• Adobe Suite

Android

Windows

• Linux

#### **Education**

### **University of Advancing Technology**

Tempe, AZ

Aug. 2013 – May 2016

- Bachelors of Science in Advancing Computer Science. GPA: 4.00
- Undergraduate course work: Database; Algorithms; Programming Languages; Engineering Principles; Linear Algebra; Advanced Software Development

# **Technical Projects**

# **Perspective Rectification Tool**

Jan. 2015 – May 2015

• JavaFX desktop application used to rectify a given image to a normalized perspective based on the user's input.

### **Network Technician Tool**

Jan. 2015 – May 2015

• Multi-platform C# mobile application containing vital networking tools such as a subnet mask calculator and network quote tool.

## **Table Top Management Tool**

Aug. 2014 – Present

• A desktop application used to manage the large database of information used to play a table top game.

#### Awards/Affiliations

- Microsoft Office Specialist
- Boy Scouts of America Eagle Scout Rank
- 2 Science Olympiad National Medals
- 3rd Place in AIA 2011 NAWIC CAD Drafting Competition
- iCritical Thinking Certification
- iC3 Certification
- Strata Certification
- National Career Readiness Certificate
- President's Education Award Achievement

## **Employment**

## **University of Advancing Technology**

Tempe, AZ

May 2015 – Aug. 2015

• I was a web development intern at UAT and I was responsible with updating UAT's main website's HTML and CSS pages.

#### **Rock Ridge Services**

Wasilla, AK

Jul. 2014 – Aug. 2014

• As a landscape technician, I was responsible for working labor jobs as a team and creating landscaping documentation